‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎Listen, Kim.
‎Let's see each other more often, okay?
‎Min-ji's grown up now.
‎He's right.
‎She'll have a boyfriend soon too.
‎What the hell?
‎What? You scared?
‎This has nothing to do with us.
‎We're middle-aged men
‎who tolerate injustice.
‎We're no longer young.
‎We're just middle-aged men with glasses.
‎Dad!
‎I'm sorry.
‎I've fallen short as a parent
‎since I'm raising her alone.
‎I ask that you find it in your heart
‎to forgive us.
‎I feel so angry, frustrated, and pathetic.
‎I don't have a mom.
‎You're all I have left.
‎They're the bad ones.
‎I'm going to make you get on your knees.
‎Hit me. I said hit me!
‎Just die!
‎My dad is Ju Gang-chan,
‎the chairman of Juhak Construction.
‎I'll pay whatever you want,
‎so just get rid of the body.
‎I owe Chairman Ju,
‎so I'm making an exception to help you.
‎Let's keep this a secret from your father.
‎Did you meet Min-ji yesterday?
‎I only heard something
‎about the back gate.
‎Can I ask a question?
‎This is your hair tie, right?
‎Hey, old man. You're dead meat.
‎Tell me. Where's Min-ji?
‎Oh Min-cheol…
‎I'm only keeping you alive
‎because I believe my daughter is.
‎If she's not, you, your friends,
‎and your family will all die.
‎I took care of the girl's body.
‎Don't answer it,
‎and get rid of that phone.
‎UNABLE TO ACCESS CONVERSATION
‎Contact them now.
‎A tier-one wanted fugitive
‎has been caught on camera.
‎Go to the South and bring me back
‎the head of the fake Number 66.
‎Director, we have a situation.
‎We can't hand over someone
‎as dangerous as Kim to the North.
‎We'll get to him first.
‎Have you heard from Kim?
‎I'll try calling him.
‎It's a dead body!
‎You should've at least
‎covered it with plastic, idiot!
‎"Access denied"?
‎I'll try it again.
‎Does that belong to him?
‎Yes, sir. We confiscated it.
‎"My daughter"?
‎5 MONTHS AGO
‎Hey.
‎Damn it.
‎Move.
‎Watch where you're going.
‎What a bitch.
‎Hey, Min-ji.
‎Lend me your phone.
‎I got caught playing games,
‎so they took my phone. I'm so annoyed.
‎I can't. What about me, then?
‎I'll give it back
‎right after fourth period.
‎Come on, we're friends.
‎We're best friends!
‎-Just until fourth period.
‎-Okay.
‎Thank you.
‎Hey.
‎What's with the crappy phone?
‎Get a new one already.
‎This looks like my dad's.
‎Thank you.
‎Look at what I got.
‎-What?
‎-What is it?
‎It's pretty, right?
‎I don't like the color.
‎It's not my style.
‎-Nothing beats the latest model.
‎-It's pretty.
‎-You know, I bet mine's more expensive.
‎-It's the latest model.
‎EPISODE 3
‎Dad, let's eat.
‎Dad!
‎What's all this?
‎Did you make this?
‎Yeah. Here, cool off in front of the fan.
‎It's hot, isn't it?
‎I may not be good at studying,
‎but I make a great spicy stir-fried pork.
‎Thanks.
‎Why aren't you eating?
‎Because adults are supposed to eat first.
‎Is everything okay at work?
‎-Yeah.
‎-Everything good?
‎Do you need anything?
‎No.
‎I'm going to the convenience store later.
‎Do you want anything?
‎No, I'm okay.
‎You've had a long day.
‎How about a massage later?
‎I'm fine.
‎I'll at least do the dishes, then.
‎It's too much for you to do alone,
‎and I'm all grown up now.
‎How much do you need?
‎I don't want money.
‎I want a new phone.
‎Is it broken?
‎No, but I've used it for over three years,
‎so it'll probably die soon.
‎Tell me when it dies.
‎No one uses their phone
‎until it dies these days.
‎The other kids get a new phone every year.
‎No, not even a year.
‎Some kids get a new one every month.
‎Want to see my phone?
‎Look at this.
‎How can I take this to school?
‎It's so embarrassing.
‎It totally sucks.
‎Or at least get a new one for yourself.
‎Forget it. I'm eating in my room.
‎Kim Min-ji!
‎It wasn't me.
‎It was the wind.
‎-I'm home.
‎-Hey.
‎Oh my gosh! What's this?
‎Wait, it's that phone!
‎Dad.
‎I love you.
‎I love you more.
‎Why did he get me this?
‎What's this?
‎It's so tacky.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎"My daughter"?
‎What the hell?
‎Hello?
‎Is that you, Min-ji?
‎Min-ji…
‎The phone you are calling is turned off.
‎You will be redirected to voicemail,
‎and charges will apply after the beep.
‎Have you located him?
‎We're still looking.
‎Why is it taking so long
‎to trace his phone?
‎We can't get into the data on the phone,
‎so tracking it by frequency alone
‎will take a while.
‎MY DAUGHTER
‎The phone you are calling is turned off.
‎You will be redirected to voicemail.
‎If he's caught on and fled,
‎there's a chance he destroyed his phone.
‎Sir, can you go faster?
‎Sir.
‎We detected a background check
‎on Codename 66 by Hwasin Police Station.
‎Head to the police station,
‎and reassign the surveillance team
‎to tracking detail.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎-Understood.
‎Should I put down last year
‎in the field here?
‎-Yes, that's right.
‎-Okay.
‎Okay.
‎Sang-a.
‎Where are you going?
‎Wow, the coffee is great today.
‎-I need to take this call.
‎-Sure.
‎Hello?
‎Yes.
‎All right, sure thing.
‎Honey.
‎Hye-ri refuses to come out of her room.
‎She's skipping school today too?
‎When I try to go in,
‎she gets mad and tells me to get out.
‎Do you happen to know
‎what her dad does for a living?
‎Why do you ask?
‎I don't know.
‎I'm just curious.
‎Find out what happened to Hye-ri.
‎Yes, sir.
‎JUHAK CONSTRUCTION CO., LTD.
‎JU HYE-RI
‎"Sung Min-ho."
‎INCOMING, OUTGOING, MISSED
‎Open the messages.
‎I REALLY WORKED MY MUSCLES TODAY
‎SHOULD I DO A FITNESS SHOOT?
‎DO WHATEVER, BUT MIND YOUR MANNERS
‎I'M AT SCHOOL, WASN'T EXPECTING THAT
‎-LOL WHY? TOO HOT FOR YOU?
‎-UGH…
‎I MISS YOU
‎-Min-ho, can you come here today?
‎-Yeah, what's up?
‎There's this girl
‎who doesn't know her place,
‎so I need to teach her a lesson.
‎Bring the others too.
‎Oh, so it's not because you miss me.
‎Who's the bitch with the nerve
‎to mess with my Hye-ri?
‎Her name is Kim Min-ji.
‎She's got such an attitude
‎and always talks back to me.
‎Okay, I'll be right there.
‎Damn it, I didn't sleep a wink.
‎Why? Don't you trust me?
‎I'll take care of everything.
‎SMH_UNTAMED: LOOKING PRETTY TODAY TOO
‎Check Sung Min-ho's account.
‎SUNG MIN-HO
‎DOWON LAUNDRY
‎STUDENT ID
‎KIM MIN-JI, SONGIN HIGH SCHOOL
‎Comrade, did you find 66?
‎Well, well.
‎You said you were hungry,
‎but it looks like you'll never eat again.
‎A VP9?
‎That thing won't go through a frying pan,
‎much less a person.
‎Is that so?
‎It went through.
‎Rock and roll!
‎Come on!
‎You son of a bitch.
‎Stop punching my stomach.
‎That's just cheap.
‎The gun!
‎The gun, the gun!
‎Hey, you bastard!
‎What the hell?
‎Oops, my knees.
‎If I were ten years younger…
‎Where is it?
‎Oh, there it is.
‎Man, this guy is something else.
‎Hold on.
‎I need to call Kim.
‎I need to let him know.
‎Damn it, the police confiscated my phone!
‎This is insane.
‎Jeez, that was a brutal fight.
‎They're so barbaric.
‎How could they do that
‎in someone else's house?
‎And why did he take off the fridge door?
‎This means Kim was arrested by the police.
‎Does that make any sense?
‎There's no other reason for his
‎background check record to show up.
‎No matter how I look at it,
‎it just doesn't add up.
‎Talk to me.
‎Someone is after Agent Kim.
‎I think it's a North Korean operative.
‎Already?
‎And Park Jin-cheol
‎showed up at the scene.
‎Even Park Jin-cheol?
‎What game are these bastards playing?
‎Sir, we have a location
‎on Agent Kim's phone.
‎Where? Is it at Hwasin Police Station?
‎No, sir.
‎GPS reads N99, E81.
‎-It's Pure Taekwondo.
‎-It's a Taekwondo studio, sir.
‎Taekwondo master, Sung Han-soo.
‎Former Olympic gold medalist in Taekwondo.
‎Three-time consecutive world champion.
‎After retiring,
‎he was recruited by the government
‎and infiltrated the North
‎with Agent Kim and Park Jin-cheol.
‎SUNG HAN-SOO
‎NIS SPECIAL RECRUIT
‎Roundhouse kick! One!
‎Two!
‎Nice and clean! Three!
‎Switch feet!
‎One!
‎Two!
‎-Instructor Choi.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Can you take the kids for ‎gubo‎?
‎What does ‎gubo‎ mean?
‎It's just running.
‎-Let's go, kids.
‎-Go for a run.
‎-Okay!
‎I was so surprised
‎that I didn't even know how to react.
‎What's going on?
‎You wouldn't have come all the way here
‎if it wasn't a big deal.
‎-I need the bunker.
‎-The bunker?
‎Did someone steal your bank book
‎and take off or something?
‎Min-ji…
‎What about her?
‎I read a message
‎saying she was dead.
‎-What did you say?
‎-But then,
‎I got a call.
‎What are you talking about?
‎Explain it so I can understand!
‎You don't even know if she's alive?
‎Where is she right now?
‎All I know is that she was kidnapped.
‎I got a call, but I couldn't answer it.
‎I need to get rid of this right now,
‎but I can't.
‎Get rid of it? Why?
‎Did you get into trouble?
‎They're probably tracking me already.
‎I'm sorry for bringing you into this.
‎Han-soo.
‎Let's trace Min-ji's phone first.
‎Wow, look who it is.
‎Someone who'd be in a bind
‎if they ran into me.
‎Master, a monster caught me.
‎Let's see here.
‎Is there someone
‎in an even bigger bind inside?
‎Are you washed-up agents
‎reminiscing about the good old days?
‎Let the kid go.
‎Hey, Taekwondo.
‎Stay out of this.
‎You're a South Korean citizen,
‎so I'll let you off the hook.
‎But Kim…
‎I mean…
‎North Korean-born 66 is different.
‎That bastard violated the contract.
‎He's exposed himself to the North,
‎is what I'm saying.
‎Let me go, monster!
‎Hey, kid.
‎The real monster is your master.
‎Just look at him.
‎Gosh, he's scary.
‎That's a lie! Master, run!
‎It's a monster!
‎Two blank rounds.
‎You haven't changed a bit.
‎It could be three. Want to shoot and see?
‎Go around to the emergency exit.
‎The emergency exit!
‎Open the door!
‎Step aside.
‎Ready.
‎-Three!
‎-Four!
‎Stand down.
‎Go after them!
‎Agent Jang, this way!
‎PURE TAEKWONDO
‎Hey.
‎I hope this still works.
‎There we go.
‎It's working.
‎It's been a while. Can you still manage?
‎You don't forget how to use your fists
‎just because it's been a while, do you?
‎I'm sorry.
‎Now the SMD is on you because of me.
‎If Tae-hun were in the same situation,
‎I'd have gone to you first too.
‎Did you forget how to drive?
‎Hurry up. Let's go find Min-ji.
‎ONCE A MARINE, ALWAYS A MARINE
‎KOREAN MARINE VETERANS FEDERATION
‎Salute!
‎Come on, hurry up.
‎They'll catch up with us soon.
‎Did you tap into the tower yet?
‎Frequency isn't locking,
‎so I'm pulling wide-area data instead.
‎Who is it?
‎It's an unknown number.
‎It could be Min-ji.
‎Give it to me. You just focus on driving.
‎-Hello--
‎-You punk!
‎You're in big trouble!
‎Some guy from the North came to kill you.
‎Be careful.
‎I should've ended him myself, but…
‎I'm sorry.
‎I couldn't jump because I have bad knees.
‎Anyway, that's not important right now.
‎Min-ji will be in danger too.
‎Where's Min-ji's school?
‎I'll go there right now.
‎Are you listening?
‎Hey! Are you listening to me?!
‎-Jeez, it's as if he's on speaker.
‎-Hey, you punk!
‎Hey, where are you? How did you get out?
‎Oh, you're with him.
‎I needed some air, so I came out.
‎You crazy bastard.
‎You can't just leave lockup for some air.
‎That's not the issue here.
‎Let's go to Min-ji right now.
‎Where's her school?
‎-She's not at school.
‎-Why?
‎We think she's been kidnapped.
‎What?!
‎Who's the goddamn bastard?!
‎Let's talk more in person.
‎I'll send you the location once I have it,
‎so get over there right away.
‎Hold on.
‎I found it.
‎Where is it?
‎Got the location.
‎It's 8-3, Gongdan-gil, Seonmin-eup,
‎Gangjang-si, Gyeonggi-do.
‎Okay, I'll meet you there.
‎Thank you for your phone, sir.
‎-Salute!
‎I'll make sure to repay this favor soon.
‎It was nothing.
‎Just buy me a coffee from there, then.
‎Oh, coffee.
‎Oh, but I left my wallet in lockup.
‎May I offer this instead of coffee?
‎-This is tasty.
‎-Right?
‎This is the next best thing to coffee.
‎Then could you lend me money
‎for transportation, sir?
‎-Transportation money?
‎-Yes, sir.
‎I'd really appreciate it, sir.
‎Who is it?
‎So you're saying
‎that girl's father did this to you.
‎He was scary as hell.
‎I'm telling you, he isn't human.
‎His body
‎is freaking covered in scars
‎and bullet wounds!
‎Goddamn it. You know whose fault it is
‎that I'm going through this hell?
‎It's all because of Hye-ri!
‎You seem pretty capable.
‎Ask the higher-ups for more money.
‎You're saying Hye-ri's involved?
‎Yes, sir.
‎Okay.
‎Get rid of any evidence first.
‎Yes, sir.
‎I assume you have no way
‎of contacting the person
‎who took Min-ji's body.
‎I seriously don't know.
‎You don't know, huh?
‎Come on, let's go!
‎-Is this it?
‎-Yeah.
‎Come here.
‎You got a death wish?
‎Does this look like 100,000 won to you?
‎But I gave it to you last week.
‎That was the late fee, you idiot.
‎Don't you know what that means?
‎What late fee? I didn't borrow any money.
‎He keeps talking back to us.
‎-We've been going easy on you, huh?
‎-No.
‎If you take 46,000 won out of 100,000 won,
‎you have 54,000 won left, right?
‎Let's make it 1,000 won a hit.
‎Let me off this time.
‎I'll bring it tomorrow,
‎even if I have to steal it.
‎Why do I have to let you off?
‎Hey, kids.
‎Which class is Kim Min-ji in?
‎Who are you?
‎Mister, we're busy right now.
‎So get lost.
‎Keep moving, or you'll get hurt.
‎I know Kim Min-ji.
‎We're in the same class.
‎I told you to get lost.
‎What's wrong with the bastard?
‎-You want to fight?
‎-I said get lost.
‎Go get Kim Min-ji.
‎She's not at school
‎because she was suspended.
‎Call her.
‎I don't know her number.
‎But you can ask Kang Hye-ryeong.
‎They're best friends,
‎so she can use Find Friends.
‎What? "Find Friends"?
‎Yes, you can check your friend's location
‎with your phone.
‎Where is she right now?
‎Min-ji has been suspended since yesterday.
‎-Suspended?
‎-Yes.
‎She violated some school policies.
‎Sorry, one more thing.
‎I heard her father came here
‎a few days ago.
‎Was there a school violence incident?
‎Goodness, school violence?
‎You can't be serious.
‎It was nothing of the sort.
‎Where did you hear such a rumor?
‎There's no such thing
‎as school violence or bullying
‎at our school.
‎No such thing.
‎I have to get going for class now.
‎Feel free to talk to the others
‎if you'd like.
‎Kang Hye-ryeong.
‎Your fingers look pretty busy
‎for someone with a headache.
‎I'm looking up ways
‎to get rid of my headache.
‎At least your mouth is in perfect health.
‎Let's go.
‎-Okay.
‎KANG HYE-RYEONG
‎I swear I'm still not feeling well.
‎Are you Kang Hye-ryeong?
‎They say you can locate friends with this.
‎You can do that, right?
‎Jeez, you scared me.
‎I almost had a heart attack.
‎How long have you been here?
‎For a while. I was waiting outside,
‎but it got too cold.
‎You should've called ahead.
‎They reassigned the surveillance team
‎to tracking detail.
‎Any leads?
‎I think the reason Agent Kim
‎went off the rails
‎has something to do with his daughter.
‎Right, so that means
‎we'll find him wherever his daughter is.
‎Why are you talking like that?
‎I just wanted to have a little fun, okay?
‎I've been working at the dry cleaners
‎for so long
‎that I can't tell if I'm an SMD agent
‎or the owner of that place.
‎I'm having an identity crisis.
‎I guess you were cut out
‎for the laundry business.
‎It could be your calling.
‎Did you pick up any clues
‎in the neighborhood?
‎No, not yet.
‎Wow, that's cutting-edge.
‎Times sure have changed.
‎This abalone is rather tough.
‎This place isn't great.
‎Don't you agree?
‎You must have a reason
‎for reaching out so suddenly.
‎I cleared out the other rooms,
‎so you can talk freely.
‎It's such a massive project
‎that I'm not sure how to explain this.
‎I guess you could say
‎it's like building an entire city
‎out in the wasteland.
‎I'm sure you saw on the news
‎that the high-level inter-Korean talks
‎will take place soon.
‎Do you know
‎what's at the top of the agenda?
‎It's to establish a free-trade zone
‎through a South-North joint venture.
‎That's good news.
‎We're in an era of peace now,
‎not confrontation.
‎For a project of this scale,
‎only a firm like Juhak Construction
‎can deliver.
‎That's just my thought, but…
‎Please continue.
‎The thing is,
‎I can't make this decision alone.
‎I need a good reason
‎to convince the other assemblymen.
‎Don't worry about the funding.
‎I'll provide whatever you need.
‎Goodness, you put it so bluntly.
‎I like that you and I
‎speak the same language.
‎If a problem can't be solved with money,
‎it's because you don't have enough.
‎And if it still doesn't work…
‎If it doesn't?
‎Just give me a list of the people
‎who can't be convinced.
‎So Min-ji has disappeared somewhere…
‎and her father is looking for her?
‎We don't have a current location on him.
‎We ran a background check,
‎but access was denied.
‎Something's off.
‎Is this the place?
‎Yeah, third floor.
‎-Let's go.
‎-Okay.
‎Seriously, man.
‎Jeez, there are so many of them.
‎Hey, mister.
‎You can't just walk in here. Please leave.
‎How did they get in?
‎Damn it. Hey, Taekwondo. Get out.
‎-What's with the uniform?
‎-Darn it.
‎I should've changed before coming.
‎I have lots of nice outfits.
‎This might take some time.
‎We don't have time.
‎We'll push through the way they would.
‎So you're going to play the thug, huh?
‎Who's the head here?
‎Is it you?
‎What a joke.
‎What head?
‎Your blockhead?
‎My guys told you to leave.
‎Get lost.
‎Let's just say it's you.
‎Songin High School, Grade 11, Class 7.
‎Brown jacket, yellow hoodie,
‎a heart keychain on her phone.
‎Has anyone seen her?
‎No, sir.
‎If not, then get out of my way.
‎Or else I'll skin you alive.
‎Which way?
‎That way.
‎-Wait.
‎-Damn it, he said not to let anyone in.
‎Then go with them!
‎You think I'm crazy?
‎What are you all doing?
‎I've got it here. You…
‎I'm in this mess
‎because I have such good friends.
‎-You need to choose your friends wisely.
‎-What's he talking about?
‎Hey, get him!
‎Boss.
‎Someone's coming.
‎I told you not to let any of the guys in.
‎It's not one of our guys.
‎It's some middle-aged guy.
‎Who cares if it's a kid or a boomer?
‎I told them to stay away, but they didn't.
‎So now they're dead.
‎Come on, I'm the queen of investing.
‎Let's study investing together.
‎I'll send you a link.
‎You want to meet up?
‎I'm a little busy this week.
‎What are you talking about?
‎There's no one else but you.
‎Hang on.
‎Sir, he keeps saying he wants to meet up.
‎How much did we get from him?
‎About 30 million won this time.
‎Just play it off. Say you're traveling.
‎Jeez, I can't do this crap anymore.
‎Hey.
‎What the hell?
‎Just leave quietly.
‎Move.
‎Didn't you hear what the boss said?
‎Sir.
‎It's not like that.
‎This bastard suddenly--
‎So you know how to box.
‎I'll pop your eyes and eardrums.
‎I'm different from the punks out there.
‎You're just a punk who knows how to box.
‎He's going to kill him.
‎Someone go and stop Hyeong-min.
‎I think that's Hyeong-min's voice.
‎Who's that old man?
‎Are you a cop?
‎You think a knife won't go through a cop?
‎They're all lumps of flesh in the end.
‎Hey, mister.
‎Didn't they tell you to stay out?
‎Hey, take him down.
‎Who wants another beating?
‎No takers? Then get out.
‎Get out!
‎Jeez, my knees.
‎Wow, that was amazing.
‎You're so cool.
‎Do you run a mobile phone store?
‎Where did you get that phone?
‎What do you mean?
‎Oh, this?
‎Where did I get this from again?
‎Hold on.
‎Let me check the photo.
‎Darn, I feel like I should remember.
‎Oh, I know.
‎It's the girl
‎I messed around with last night.
‎Kim!
‎Are you going to kill him?
‎We need to ask him where Min-ji is.
‎Think carefully before you answer.
‎Do you know who Kim Min-ji is?
‎I don't.
‎I've never seen her before.
‎I swear!
‎Then tell me.
‎Where did you get this from?
‎The thing is…
‎Damn.
‎That's a nice phone. How about this?
‎Ta-da.
‎Want to trade?
‎-Hello, sir.
‎-Hello.
‎-Show us your haul.
‎-On the table.
‎Be gentle, man.
‎Did you unlock them?
‎Yes, we unlocked the ones
‎to sell as burners.
‎And I told the guys
‎to fix the ones with cracked screens.
‎Hyeong-min.
‎Any girls' phones?
‎Are there any with sexy bikini photos?
‎I have a good feeling about this.
‎I think she'll be pretty.
‎Let me see.
‎Oh, look at that.
‎She's pretty cute.
‎This is it?
‎How boring.
‎Keep going.
‎DAD
‎I knew it.
‎Her dad is the only one
‎in her call history.
‎I guess she only has her dad.
‎Hey.
‎Bring me another one.
‎Hello?
‎-Is that you, Min-ji?
‎-What the hell?
‎Damn it, I pressed the wrong button.
‎DAD
‎So I turned off the phone right away.
‎Hold on.
‎What did you just say?
‎I turned off the phone.
‎No.
‎Before that.
‎About the call history.
‎I only saw "Dad" in it.
‎There wasn't a single friend.
‎Oh.
‎HYE-RYEONG
‎There was one.
‎Kang Hye-ryeong.
‎I need the name of a close friend
‎and their phone number.
‎-Kim Min-ji!
‎-Kang Hye-ryeong.
‎Her number is 010-0610-6003.
‎I'm staying at Hye-ryeong's tonight,
‎so don't call me.
‎But I don't know
‎if I'd call her a friend.
‎Min-ji, can I borrow 20,000 won?
‎Can you lend me your phone?
‎Lend me your phone.
‎What's with the crappy phone?
‎Lend me your gym clothes.
‎Thank you.
‎Sorry, I lost your gym clothes.
‎It's my birthday tomorrow.
‎Can you buy me foundation?
‎It looked like…
‎she was just using her.
‎I had no idea.
‎I pray
‎For you
‎You'll be protected
‎So that my hopes reach you--
‎Kim Min-ji.
‎At least help me clean
‎if you're staying home on the weekend.
‎Why are you holed up in your room?
‎Go hang out with your friends instead.
‎It's hot outside.
‎It's hot in your room too.
‎Take this and come out.
‎I didn't do anything wrong.
‎She and her girls kept harassing me.
‎I took it for as long as I could
‎before fighting back!
‎Kim Min-ji.
‎Be quiet.
‎Jeez, wash your clothes.
‎I said don't look at me like that!
‎That's enough.
‎Stop picking on that pathetic kid.
‎Come out.
‎Why?
‎Why didn't I notice sooner?
‎Hey.
‎Get it together.
‎There's no time to get emotional.
‎It must've been so hard for her.
‎My poor Min-ji…
‎I know you've tried hard.
‎And I know you're hurting a lot.
‎Han-soo.
‎But you're her dad.
‎So let's find Min-ji first.
‎You can't apologize unless you do.
‎So?
‎Where did you get this again?
‎Sorry?
‎At Hwasin Station.
‎I took it from a homeless man.
‎Let's go.
‎Here you are.
‎Fake 66.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎EPILOGUE
‎Name?
‎Age?
‎Family?
‎Right.
‎What's the point of any of this?
‎Your name and identity
‎are all a secret anyway, right?
‎Why are you keeping me alive?
‎That's a good question.
‎Well, let's see.
‎Killing you won't speed up reunification.
‎And depending on the situation,
‎we might be able to help each other out.
‎I have this feeling
‎that you could be
‎of some sort of help to us.
‎Yeah, a gut feeling.
‎Are you asking me to betray my homeland?
‎Goodness.
‎How can a man with no name, age, or family
‎have a homeland?
‎Here comes the guy
‎who hunts down people like you.
‎Come in.
‎Goodness.
‎Look who's here to grace this fine place
‎with their lowly presence.
‎It's Park Jin-cheol.
‎Life or death.
‎Fight to the end!
‎From up north
‎and down south.
‎Go on.
‎Greet your fellow top dog.
‎Is this that buddy?
‎He's not quite a buddy yet.
‎Hey, comrade.
‎Before we decide
‎whether you'll be our buddy or a commie,
‎let's assess your skills first.
‎Don't kill him just yet.
‎A soldier either kills or gets killed.
‎Don't hold back
‎if you want to live.
‎If I want to live?
‎I have no desire to live.
‎I'm just…
‎keeping the promise I made
‎to my only friend.
‎I like that.
‎What's your name?
‎It's 73.
‎No.
‎It's 66.
‎Bring it on, 66.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎I expected someone would be watching me.
‎If he doesn't want his precious daughter
‎to go to prison…
‎Crush him.
‎Stop!
‎What are you, a damn deer?!
‎You know whose phone this is, don't you?
‎Did you check if she was dead?
‎Promise me…
‎you'll survive.
‎I'll take good care of the body
‎in the meantime.
‎Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim